Yes, we get Superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in
United gently bringing
up our thought again,
yeah We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The bonds built between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes, we're the superpowers
Superpowers
Yes, we're the superpowers
Give it to me
You sure you're okay with this, Chiffon?
Yeah, thank you, sweetie.
I'm certain.
They definitely took one hell
of a challenge, didn't we?
Bumping her off might
have to take a back seat
while we figure out how
we're gonna blow this joint.
Don't be like that, Veggie!
We agreed to help Nami and her friends
escape, and that's what we'll do!
It's too late to wimp out now
just to save our own hides!
This is how you properly pay back a debt!
Take it easy.
Believe in the cake's flavor.
Blackleg did an extraordinary job on it.
Damn it, Chiffon.
That's what I love about you, baby.
I can see my cake!
Let's ditch these rules.
I hope you're ready for this.
You're good-for-nothing pirates!
There's another ship gaining on us!
It's Sweet General Smoothie's ship!
Big Mom may have left, but this
is still quite troublesome.
Careful!
That's the weird squeezing lady!
Smoothie, you're here too?
How long will it take
to get to Kaku Island?
We're still about three hours out!
We should be arriving there at
1am, exactly as we promised!
Yeah, but we have one major problem.
We don't know when or where
Luffy is going to pop up,
and we can't warn him of
the danger ahead of time.
I believe I have a plan that could work.
It should get us through this mess.
Oven, sir.
There are more and more
ships surrounding the area.
Are we sure this is necessary?
It's just...
I can't really see General Katakuri
letting Straw Hat walk away, you know?
Shut up.
I'm just doing what Montour told me.
We need every unit.
Just trust me, okay?
Did you hear this crap?
It turns out that big explosion on the
Shit was a setup from the Straw Hats, too.
You're joking.
They may not look like
much, but at this point,
it would be a mistake if
we underestimated them.
If we let them escape,
we'll never live it down!
All right, I understand.
We will ensure their journey ends here.
Listen up!
In approximately three hours at 1 a .m.,
the stragglers of the Straw
Hat crew plan to meet up here.
They will try to reunite
with their captain.
Think of this as the last
chance to have our revenge.
To not hold back. Sir!
If by some chance Straw
Hat does manage to survive,
he's going to emerge from a mirror
located somewhere on the island.
So I need you to go into your homes
and break every single mirror in town.
Don't question my orders, just do it.
But sir, some of them
are family heirlooms.
We can't take him too lightly.
If you wish to spare a few,
sink them in the ocean.
We can salvage them later.
My point is simple.
This should be the only unbroken
mirror on this entire island.
And absolutely no exceptions.
Don't try me!
Should I find out that anyone here allowed
Straw Hat to escape from their own mirror,
your whole family will be executed.
Now go!
Yasuie, sir!
We'll be waiting for you,
Straw Hat. That's right.
I'm looking forward to when you
learn that this is no ordinary exit.
This is your entrance to hell.
My apologies, I failed to
notice her needles at first.
That was quite foolish of me. Don't worry.
About fairness, this is
a fight between pirates.
It's all my fault for not
being able to dodge them.
For the record,
I no longer think that you're
inferior to me really all right,
thanks. I guess.
Dodge me 100 times.
Failing this routine will
mean no dinner for you!
Sounds awful, right? Then focus.
Gotcha!
Thinking your opponent would
attack from the front is naive.
You'll find reading an
animal's mind is easy,
as they show their emotions on their face.
However, interpreting a
human is vastly different.
We can deceive others
and defy expectations.
Ouch!
F-f-fair!
I'm hungry!
You're a fool if you
think an enemy would stop
attacking just because
you need a lunch break.
There's intent behind
every attack by him, too.
I smell something delicious.
Don't pay that any mind.
Just my dinner.
Gotcha!
Over there!
You can't go attacking
your foe blindly, Luffy.
That hurt, Rayleigh.
I get it, I get it.
I can feel your anger.
That's a part of Haki too.
Sharpen your senses.
You must feel your enemy's presence.
I said I feel your anger!
I'm hungry.
Someone there?
Get lost, you guys.
I can't take food from you.
Well, Fraley says I don't
get to eat, and no dinner.
Come on, Lucy. Focus.
It's interesting.
Your observation hockey's a bit peculiar.
It appears to be attuned to the emotions
of not only people, but animals, too.
Though it's unconscious, I'm sure.
Is that bad? Of course not.
It's quite a useful skill.
Having that ability means you can sense
the next actions your opponent will take.
Make sure to practice this talent.
Those who master it can even
glimpse into the future.
That's crazy!
What are you going to do if you
come across someone like that?
Think you can take them on?
Just two years of training
won't cut it, you know.
It'll be tough.
It'll kind of depend on what they're like.
Hmm?
Their personality?
Why's that matter?
I've never thought of it that way.
Why wouldn't you?
You're quite the odd fellow.
I mean, think.
That's what it might come down to.
You're going to have some
tough times, without a doubt.
With that in mind, we can't
afford to rest for long.
I'll get the next lesson underway.
Come on.
Yeah!
I'm going to teach you everything
I can before your stay is up.
I'm so glad to see you.
Oh, that's all.
Oh, my God.
Burning mochi!
Ah!
If she catches up, we're toast a little.
Nah, we're good.
Don't forget who has the cake.
They wouldn't dare touch us.
Besides, at that size, Prometheus
ain't quite as nimble no more.
We'll reach La Karoo Island, so
don't you sweat at one thing.
Thanks to the quick patch-up job on
our paddles, we're back to hauling ass.
You done excellent work, fellas. Thanks!
That's awfully kind!
So we'll launch Land the cake onto the
island and make a break for it, right?
Yup, that's the plan.
Hold up, not yet.
What's the matter?
LaCour Island is too close.
I think we should lure her
to Fluffy Island instead.
What kind of harebrained idea is that?
Listen, Mama's having hunger pangs now.
But what do you think will happen
after she has a fill of cake?
She's going to come to her senses as what?
We have to give Nami more distance
or she'll go right for them.
What's so wrong with that?
We gotta put ourselves first.
We're gonna belly up
if we get sloppy here.
You see that?
Mama's a monster, even more than usual.
My cake!
I'm dying to get a bite.
There you are.
My precious care.
We'll be together at last.
Now that you get what I'm saying?
Uh-huh.
We're still going to Fluffy Island.
Weren't you listening to me?
I must pay back my debt to the Straw Hats.
Even if it will cost me my own life.
I've already made up my mind.
I'll go by myself if I have to.
There's been a change of plans.
To Fluffy Island on a double!
That's the reason you're my gal, Siobhan.
You always outdoes yourself, baby.
All right, let's get a move on it, boys.
Okay, if you say so far, we'll do it.
Be right back!
Be careful, okay, Sanji?
Will do You better not inch
any closer, you hear me, Sanji?
Keep sharp and don't drop your guard.
Take care of the Sonny, okay? Roger.
All right, Pudding.
Let's head to the island.
Don't you dare pull
that crap on me, mister.
How could you lure me around
like some kind of bossy husband?
Sonny!
Huh?
What was that?
Carrot.
Feeling better already?
I'm sorry, everyone.
I didn't mean to sleep for so long.
No need to apologize.
Guys, you made your Cho-Bro proud.
During a full moon, do Cat Viper and
Dogstorm do that cool transformation too?
All Minks can do it.
If you thought I was impressive,
wait till you see them.
They're way stronger.
Whoa.
Touch the enemy and let me know which
direction they're attacking from!
On it! No!
Hurry!
I need more liquid than that.
Don't you think you're going a little far?
That man is one of your own.
There's no more room for failure.
I'll get this done.
What is that?
It looks like a giant woman to me.
Can I see your giant panties, baby?
Get off, you bony creep!
Here comes another!
Oh, my room's covered!
We're gonna die!
Deepay, no hard support!
Fishman!
Stay on your toes, everyone!
Our survival depends on your directions!
He's coming to us!
Mount and clear!
I've got your back for sure, Deepay!
Oh, he's going even larger!
That's enough!
At this rate, you're gonna sink our ship!
I meant to go! Now!
Oh no!
You gotta be kidding me!
This is the end!
D-Page, dodge the starboard!
Hang on for your dear lives!
This is gonna be rough!
Such annoying little tests!
Thank you.
I appreciate all the help you've given me.
Cut that crap out!
Stay away!
Don't leave that corner!
Okay, Sanji.
Dear, I don't want to be mistaken
as your wife. No one's here.
So, uh, anyway, you don't think
this will actually work, do you?
I wish Luffy didn't have quite so
many enemies waiting on Kaku Island.
But I'm gonna work it out.
I will save my captain.
How's the operation going?
As ordered, you won't find a
single mirror on the island.
You'll also be happy to know that your
siblings are starting to arrive, sir.
Uh, sir? Very good.
This is making me kind of uneasy.
I've never seen so many
family members here.
Do you really think this is necessary
to capture that straw-eyed guy?
How many foes are headed our way?
Around ten, sir.
That's all?
Good night.
Wake me up if something happens. Yes, sir.
The worst generation, huh?
Let's make an example of these guys.
Maybe then the others
will get the message.
My pride as a former
general is on the line.
Summoning all these forces
to fight a handful will pass.
A shameful day for the Big Mom Pirates.
Or are they truly a force of nature?
Only time will tell.
How sure are you?
This seems a bit excessive.
It's just like a festival—let's party!
Oh,
shut your traps!
Just lend us a hand; we need everyone.
Damn that Straw Hat humiliating us at the
tea party—we'll take his head as revenge.
The first time we were sent after him,
we should have made sure
he was dealt with properly.
Now he and his friends
have made a mockery of us.
Give me
a break—this is so annoying now.
That we can't track them
with our territory slugs.
But there's an
awful lot of us here.
This should be a cinch.
We'll find out soon, won't we?
We've got about an hour left.
There's no room for error.
They're all finished
this time approximately.
this time approximately Only
one hour remains until the
Straw Hats are supposed to
reconvene on Kaku Island.
What's wrong, Straw Hats?
Is that all you've got? No.
Just give me a sec.
Stand up now!
Yes, I accept the challenge.
I'm wrapping this up.
Let's see how this one will go. Let's.
I welcome it.
This is it!
I know.
Fourth gear!
Let's go.
Snake-man!
Snake-man, huh?
And how's that different
than the last one?
Unlike Bounce-man, this
form is designed for speed.
Your Haki can't keep up!
He'll see!
Just one punch after all that bragging.
What the hell was that?
Why is it coming from the side?
I see the punch clearly.
Then something strange happens.
First I dodge and then I
see so that's how it works
This is far from over!
I'm still stronger and faster.
Your tricks are nothing.
Hacksaw!
I've caught Mochi!
Damn, it's too sticky!
I can't get it off!
I'm getting dizzy!
Stop!
I don't like this!
Let me go!
Damn it!
I can't get this stuff off!
Sorry, Straw Heart.
It's over.
Are you kidding me?!
Oh,
my God.
This hurts!
You're tough!
And I'm hungry!
Is that all you wanted to say to me?
Yeah, and I feel a lot better now!
There's only one thing left!
And that's to kick your ass!
Now, I'm going to jet cover it!
It's over!
Hard smoking!
Damn you, Straw Hat!
Where'd they?
Uuh!
Uh!
Python!
Uh! Wuh!
Right there !εν!
Why'd they?
What's the?
You?
Aaaahhh!
Almost!
What's next?
That looks fun.
Come on. Okay.
There's no charging this!
Come, come!
Come, come! Come, come!
SCREAMING
After this attack, it's over.
Are you telling me you're ready to quit?
Cause I'm not.
That move, huh?
I'll put you out of your misery.
I'm good, thanks!
I keep thinking of Monkey.
I hope he's alright out there.
Haven't heard any news.
Keep rising higher, Luffy.
Now come on!
First time, Moji!
King Pobra! Come on!
There's no escape now!